all right we're gonna be looking at the
whole medics foot pleaser today
hopefully it's awesome so let's go give
it a try all right it does seem to be
foot operated which is awesome you press
the button here and it starts twirling
round and round see how that is well
with my big feet on it it slows down
considerably but it still works it's
struggling it's struggling you got you
got fat guy on you let's see what press
it again and it's like a disco man and I
think the red would imply there's heats
I don't want to put too much pressure on
it because I'm afraid I'm going to break
the thing it does seem durable though oh
these little ball bearings man they're
just they're working I'm telling you
they're dirt they're doing the best they
can
oh wow it's a very strange sensation
it's very very strange
i I guess it's good I mean I'm not one
of those people that you know needs a
foot massage a lot I can feel it warming
up a little bit yeah it is it is getting
a little warm so the red definitely
means warm
and I guess this is just regular I mean
it's not bad it's okay
I mean you know when I saw the thing I
expected it to twirl around and it
twirls around so I'd give this product
to sure why not if you're if you're into
foot massages and that sort of thing you
know what I'm saying it does slow down
considerably when I put pressure on it
though that that would kind of imply
that if I do that a lot I'll probably
break it so I kind of questioned its
durability but you know it does work and
I did get it at a garage sale somewhere
so you know hey what are you gonna do
you know I mean anyway do you have one
of these gadgets let me know what you
think thanks for watching you have a
wonderful day and I'll see you all on
the flip side I'm out
[Music]
you